<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="80">
    <author>Achimobil</author>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>Buying Price Difficulty Correction</en>
        <de>Einkaufspreisanpassung An Schwierigkeitsgrad</de>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en>
            <![CDATA[Simple mod to adjust the buying prices of buying stations to the difficulty level so that money cannot be cheated on MP servers through cheap buying and expensive selling.

In the FS, prices are all defined for the economy on Hard. If you now play on Easy, the sales prices are increased by a factor. However, the purchase prices are not. This does not matter on standard maps, as you can only buy seeds, for example, and not sell them. With mods and on mod maps, however, you can now also sell the bulk goods that you can buy. On an economy level other than Hard, this means that you can buy seeds cheaply and sell them at a high price and thus cheat in multiplayer. If you want to prevent this, simply use this mod. The mod increases the purchase prices of bulk goods and liquids and purchase silos by the same factor as the sales prices, so that there is no imbalance. 

The prices at the vehicle dealer are not affected by this. The sales prices are still subject to fluctuation through the economic system and the purchase prices remain constant.

This correction is already included in Production Revamp and can be activated there in the menu.
This mod is intended for servers on which Revamp cannot be used or on which you do not want to use Revamp.]]>
        </en>
        <de>
            <![CDATA[Einfacher Mod um die EK Preise von Kaufstationen an den Schwierigkeitsgrad an zu passen so dass nicht durch billigen EK und teuren VK Geld auf MP Servern gecheatet werden kann.

Im LS werden Preise alle für die Wirtschaft auf Schwer definiert. Spielt man nun auf Einfach, so werden die Verkaufspreise um einen Faktor erhöht. Die Einkaufspreise jedoch nicht. Auf Standard Karten ist dies Egal, da man z.B. Saatgut nur kaufen und nicht verkaufen kann. Durch Mods und auf Mod Maps kann man aber nun die Schütgüter die man kaufen kann auch verkaufen. Auf einer anderen Wirtschaftsstufe als Schwer bedeutet das man kann z.B. Saatgut billig einkaufen und teuer wieder verkaufen und so im Mutiplayer Betrügen. Wer dies verhindern will nutzt einfach dieses Mod. Der Mod erhöht die Einkaufspreise von Schüttgut und Flüssigkeiten and Kaufsilos um den gleichen Faktor wie die Verkaufspreise, so dass kein Ungleichgewicht entsteht. 

Die Preise beim Fahrzeughändler werden hierdurch nicht beeinflusst. Die Verkaufspreise unterliegen auch weiterhin einer Schwankung durch das Wirtschaftssystem und die Einkaufspreise beleiben konstant.

Diese Korrektur ist in Production Revamp bereits enthalten und kann dort im Menü aktiviert werden.
Dieser Mod ist für Server gedacht auf denen Revamp nicht benutzt werden kann oder auf denen man Revamp nicht benutzen will.]]>
        </de>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon_BuyingPriceDifficultyCorrection.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="BuyingPriceDifficultyCorrection.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>
</modDesc>